<?xml version="1.0"?>
<ArrayOfFlub xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <Flub>
    <Name>Method</Name>
    <Flubs>
      <Flub>
        <Name>Blend</Name>
        <Description>Blends the values of the two inputs.</Description>
      </Flub>
      <Flub>
        <Name>Add</Name>
        <Description>Adds Input2 to Input1.</Description>
      </Flub>
      <Flub>
        <Name>Screen</Name>
        <Description>Adds Input2 to Input1 without overexposing the output.</Description>
      </Flub>
      <Flub>
        <Name>Subtract</Name>
        <Description>Subtracts Input2 from Input1.</Description>
      </Flub>
      <Flub>
        <Name>Multiply</Name>
        <Description>Multiplies Input1 by Input2.</Description>
      </Flub>
      <Flub>
        <Name>Divide</Name>
        <Description>Divides Input1 by Input2.</Description>
      </Flub>
      <Flub>
        <Name>Max</Name>
        <Description>Selects the higher of the two inputs.</Description>
      </Flub>
      <Flub>
        <Name>Min</Name>
        <Description>Selects the lower of the two inputs.</Description>
      </Flub>
      <Flub>
        <Name>SqRt</Name>
        <Description>The square root of the two combined terrains.</Description>
      </Flub>
      <Flub>
        <Name>Power</Name>
        <Description>Uses Input2 to create exponents of Input1.</Description>
      </Flub>
      <Flub>
        <Name>Difference</Name>
        <Description>Creates the difference of the two inputs.</Description>
      </Flub>
      <Flub>
        <Name>Insert</Name>
        <Description>Insert relatively flat and isolated shapes into an uneven surface, such as sand dunes, while retaining the flatness of the rocks..</Description>
      </Flub>
      <Flub>
        <Name>Embed</Name>
        <Description>Embed any shape into any other terrain.</Description>
      </Flub>
    </Flubs>
  </Flub>
  <Flub>
    <Name>Ratio</Name>
    <Description>The ratio applied to the selected method.</Description>
  </Flub>
  <Flub>
    <Name>Swap Inputs</Name>
    <Description>Switches the two inputs.</Description>
  </Flub>
  <Flub>
    <Name>Separation Mask</Name>
    <Description>When enabled, creates a separation mask that separates the original elements from the combined output.</Description>
  </Flub>
  <Flub>
    <Name>Clamp Output</Name>
    <Description>Clamp the output between 0..1 values, removing any excess spikes or out-of-bound values.</Description>
  </Flub>
  <Flub>
    <Name>Abs</Name>
    <Description>When enabled, any value above 0.0 is forced to become 1.0. This is useful for creating hard boundaries out of masks.</Description>
  </Flub>
  <Flub>
    <Name>Threshold</Name>
    <Description>When abs is enabled, it is the threshold for the Abs operation. When Insert mode is active, it responds to the threshold to which insertion should take place.</Description>
  </Flub>
  <Flub>
    <Name>Flatten</Name>
    <Description>The amount of flattening the local terrain must go through to insert an uneven shape. Only available in Insert mode.</Description>
  </Flub>
  <Flub>
    <Name>Threshold</Name>
    <Description>The extent of insertion or embedding. Use it to multiply the Ratio value. Only available in Insert or  mode.</Description>
  </Flub> 
</ArrayOfFlub>